

Artur Korra

Java Software Developer

About Me

Hello! I am Artur Korra. I have finished the studies at the University of Elbasan. Since I finished the university EasyMarine was the first company where I started my career as a Java Software Developer. With 3 years of experience in Java and other technologies related to, I have grown my skills to work on big projects with passion and determination to reach out to the objectives. I have the abilities and the commitment to learn and going through new challenges.

Age 26

Email arturi25turi@gmail.com

Phone +355684388951

Address Elbasan 3001 Albania

Language English

Professional Skills

Communication
Effective Time Management
Computer Skills
MySQL
Spring Framework
Java
JPA
Eclipse IDE
JSF
ICEfaces
Ability to Work in a Team
GeoServer
EclipseLink
Selenium WebDriver
Thymeleaf
PrimeFaces

Microservices
Kula amata a
Kubernetes
Ability to Work Under Pressure
HTML & CSS
Git
JavaScript
Maven
Hibernate
JavaFX
Apache Tomcat
Analytical Skills
Ability to Multitask
jQuery
Derby DB
Eclipse RCP
Jasper Report



Jenkins

REST APIs

Equinox

Experience

Java BE Developer Landmark-Technologies (Sisal.it)

Feb, 2021 - Present

Working with spring technologies and microservice.

Remmote Java Software Developer EasyMarine

Feb, 2021 - Present

After I moved away from EasyMarine, they offered me the possibility to work remotely with full flexibility.

Freelancer Java Software Developer WorldWide

Feb, 2021 - Present

Working with different and small project worldwide.

Full Stack Java Software Developer EasyMarine

Oct, 2018 - Feb, 2021

Easy Marine offers digital service solutions about digitalization for the sea

shipping sector. Starting from 2007 the company has built big systems for helping the crew and company office to have under control documents and different procedures requested by law. Since I started working at Easy Marine they trusted me to work on almost all company projects. Also, I have offered support to company customers.

Education

Masters in Economics Informatics from University of Aleksander Xhuvani

2017 - 2018

Modules: Web Programming (HTML, CSS, JavaScript), Object-Oriented Programming in Java, C++, Database, Algorithm, Computer Networks, Information Security, Operating Systems, Cryptography, Computer Architecture. Master's Degree evaluation from 4-10. Result *10*.

Bachelor in Economics Informatics from University of Aleksander Xhuvani

2014 - 2017

Modules: Web Programming (HTML, CSS, JavaScript), Object-Oriented Programming in Java, C++, Database, Algorithm, Computer Networks, Information Security, Operating Systems, Cryptography, Computer Architecture. Bachelor's Degree evaluation from 4-10. Result *9*.

Projects

Marpol Desktop APP

Oct, 2018 - Jan, 2019

Marpol is a desktop app used to calculate allowed ship pollution based on Marpol Annexes. The software calculates the allowed pollution based on the ship location by reading shapefiles. The technologies used: Eclipse, Equinox, Maven, Bundle, DerbyDB, JavaFX. My task was to read shapefiles based on the location of the ship and show the calculation result for allowed and not allowed emission and pollution.

eShipManager WEB APP

Oct, 2018 - Present

EASY and EASYOFFICE ship manager. The technologies used to develop this system: for DB MYSQL to interact with DB Hibernate, JEE, JSF and ICEfaces. Two big java web app platforms. Easy is used to run on the ship using the tomcat server and EasyOffice can be run anywhere and is been used for the ship's owner office. Two apps communicate together and transfer data between each other like documents, messages, etc. Easy and EasyOffie were existing projects and I have been working to fix different bugs change different integration and also developing new modules.

easymarine.it Company Web

Jan, 2020 - Feb, 2020

Is the official company website. It is a project that I worked on and developed alone from scratch. The technologies used: Maven, JPA, Spring, Thymeleaf. Please for more follow https://www.easymarine.it/.

NavigationRobot Crawler WEB APP

Apr, 2020 - Jun, 2020

Navigation contains information for the specific locations in the world and is used to show on the map using KML files. NavigationRobot is a crawler web app that is used to take information from different websites where the navigations are published. The app uses selenium for site navigation and

after processing all the information generates KML files updated every week. All this process was done manually before I developed this app. The technologies used: Maven, JPA, Spring, Thymeleaf. Also, this was a project from scratch which I developed alone.

LogBook Desktop APP

Oct, 2019 - Oct, 2020

LogBook is a desktop app used to save ship logs operation types. Bunkering, de-bunkering, and discharging of different oils at sea is a sensitive case and regulated by law. LogBook is used to save all logs as the law request it. The technologies used: Eclipse, Equinox, Maven, Bundle, DerbyDB, EclipseLink, JavaFX. On this project, I have been working with my team leader and we developed it from scratch.

Smartload Desktop APP

Oct, 2020 - Present

Smart Load is a desktop app used to calculate ship stability at sea based on tank weight, volume filled, tank types, tank position, and ship specifications. The technologies used: Eclipse, Equinox, Maven, Bundle, DerbyDB, EclipseLink, JavaFX. We started this project with my team leader also from scratch.

API Demo Online Store

Feb. 2021 - Present

Tools to be used Java 8-10-11 Spring or SpringBoot Hibernate MySQL Dialect Description The client needs an API to manage and sell his products. The product has a name, a description, a category, the quantity in the inventory, CreatedOn, CreatedBy, ModifiedOn and Modified By. The products belong to one of the following categories: Woodworking, Tools, Garden, Automotive, Bricolage. There are two types of user: Customer and

Employee. The employee can add/edit/remove the products, the customer can view a list of products and order them one at a time (no cart needed). There will be no login functionality but with each request will contain a Userld that will be used to determine the permissions. The quantity cannot be a negative number. We need to have: A swagger interface to test the API The ability to create automatically the DB structure on an empty DB A seed function that will create two employee and three customer default users named emp1, emp2, cust1, cust2, cust3 and two default products for each category. For source code please follow:

https://github.com/arturkorra/onlineshop/

Notices To Mariners Desktop APP

Apr, 2021 - Present

The app downloads "Notices to Mariners" published on the official UK FTP and merges all the information to save the data as an inventory for each different ship that will use the app. The technologies used: Eclipse, Equinox, Maven, Bundle, DerbyDB, EclipseLink, JavaFX. I developed this app alone from scratch.

Atena Web App (Online Casino)

Feb. 2021 - Present

Working with spring framework and microservice. The technologies used: Maven, Spring Framework, ReactJS, Oracle DB, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins.

Sogei Web App (Online Casino)

Feb, 2021 - Present

Working with spring framework and microservice. The technologies used: Maven, Spring Framework, ReactJS, Oracle DB, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins.

Contact